- 514-776-8946
- archontoulagittas@hotmail.com
- 8790 rue le Corbusier, Saint-Léonard, Montréal

TOULA GITTAS

Interior Designer

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Interior Design Algonquin College 2018-2020

Interior Design Dawson College 2015-2018

SKILLS

AutoCAD

REVIT

Adobe Photoshop

Floor Plan Analysis

Furniture Procurement

Effective Time Management

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Interpersonal Communication

LANGUAGE

English

French

ABOUT ME

Highly motivated and dedicated technical interior designer seeking to utilize my skills for the advancement of the next team I have the pleasure of joining. Adapt in effectively managing a wide variety of design projects and responsibilities to support the success of an office. In my 5+ years of experience, I have designed many types of spaces using several different styles that best suite the clients' needs.

WORK EXPERIENCE

O Aug. 2021 - Present Fulhaus Inc. | CP 42509 CSP Snowdon, MTL, QC

Technical Interior Designer

Specialize in residential, commercial, and hospitality projects. Responsibilities consist of analyzing floor plans and creating FF&E plans, communicating with sales to assist in upselling, providing the client and install team with precise and legible floor plans, FF&E specs, designing mood boards, and designing interiors. Grew skills in client presentation, creating concise documents, understanding the industry of procurement and fulfillment, material/finishes (contract grade), and budgeting.

Mar. 2021 - Aug. 2021 Centre Design Réalité l 1856 Blvd. des Laurentides, LVL, QC Sales Design Consultant

Specialized in residential remodeling for kitchens and bathrooms. Grew skills in sales and communication. Responsible for selling projects, creating quotes/contracts, and designing remodels with specifications/detailed plans. Managing projects from the start to the end of the installation. Learned 2020, a 3D software program, and French courses to better my communication skills with clients.

Feb. 2019 - Aug. 2019 Lessard Design & Associates | 3978 St-André Street, MTL, QC Interior Designer

Mainly worked in residential and hospitality projects; including condos, hotels, penthouses, and more. Responsibilities revolved around updating floor plans (electrical, ceiling, ff8e), creating detailed millwork drawings, and upkeep of the materials room. Occasionally, joining the head of design on-site visits, book meetings with sales representatives for furniture/finishes vendors, and creating 3D visuals.

- 514-776-8946
- archontoulagittas@hotmail.com
- 8790 rue le Corbusier, Saint-Léonard, Montréal

TOULA GITTAS

Designer d'Intérieur

ÉDUCATION

Bacc. en Design d'Intérieur Algonquin College 2018-2020

Design d'Intérieur Dawson College 2015-2018

COMPÉTENCES

AutoCAD

REVIT

Adobe Photoshop

Analyse du Plan d'Étage

Approvisionnement des Meubles

Gestion Efficace du Temps

Capacité à Travailler sous Pression

Communication Interpersonnelle

LANGUE

Anglais

Français

À PROPOS DE MOI

Designer d'intérieur technique très motivé et dévoué, cherchant à utiliser mes compétences pour l'avancement de la prochaine équipe que j'ai le plaisir de rejoindre. S'adapter à la gestion efficace d'une grande variété de projets de conception et de responsabilités pour soutenir le succès d'un bureau. Au cours de mes plus de 5 années d'expérience, j'ai conçu de nombreux types d'espaces en utilisant plusieurs styles différents qui répondent le mieux aux besoins du client.

L'EXPÉRIENCE PROFESSIONNELLE

Août 2021 - Présent Fulhaus Inc. | CP 42509 CSP Snowdon, MTL, QC

Designer d'Intérieur Technique

Spécialisé dans les projets résidentiels, commerciaux et hôteliers. Les responsabilités consistent à analyser les plans d'étage et à créer des plans FF8E, à communiquer avec les ventes pour aider à la vente incitative, à fournir au client et à l'équipe d'installation des plans d'étage précis et lisibles, des spécifications FF8E, à concevoir des tableaux d'ambiance et à concevoir des intérieurs. Compétences accrues en matière de présentation client, de création de documents concis, de compréhension du secteur de l'approvisionnement et de l'exécution, des matériaux/finitions (qualité contractuelle) et de la budgétisation.

Mars 2021 - Août 2021

Centre Design Réalité | 1856 Blvd. des Laurentides, LVL, QC

Consultant en Design Conception

Spécialisé dans la rénovation résidentielle de cuisines et de salles de bains. Développement de compétences en vente et en communication. Responsable de la vente de projets, de la création de devis/contrats et de la conception de rénovations avec spécifications/plans détaillés. Gestion des projets du début à la fin de l'installation. J'ai appris en 2020 un logiciel 3D et des cours de français pour améliorer mes compétences en communication avec les clients.

Fevr. 2019 - Août 2019

Lessard Design & Associates | 3978 St-André Street, MTL, QC

Designer d'Intérieur

A principalement travaillé dans des projets résidentiels et hôteliers; y compris les condos, les hôtels, les penthouses et plus encore. Les responsabilités tournaient autour de la mise à jour des plans d'étage (électricité, plafond, ff8e), de la création de dessins de menuiserie détaillés et de l'entretien de la salle des matériaux. Occasionnellement, rejoindre le responsable de la conception lors de visites sur site, réserver des rendez-vous avec des représentants commerciaux pour les fournisseurs de meubles/finitions et créer des visuels 3D